Map title: "De_Runoff_ Hotrap" (hot traps)
- Bomb/Defuse mission

Background story:
- In the country there is a big chaos! The political opposition began open rebellion. It feels like the Apocalypse is near.
Some small terrorist groups, who call themselves as rebels, are now engaged in a serious subversion.
Now you're on the power station (electricity generation station, power plant), near the border of the country, not far from City 17. This station is temporarily closed and working at half capacity.
--------------
Terrorists: Take advantage of the chaos in the country and attack the power station! This will help to partially paralyze the government army, who sold their ass to the alien aggressors. Be careful - these cowardly bastards in the urgent order everything around mined with explosive barrels and so making "hot traps".

1. For the beginning blow up a control panel of the station (in point A).
2. It would be quite good to blow up still the transshipment bridge (in point B).

Other Notes: The bridge is situated towards the end of station.
Attention! Special Forces are very well armed with standard earthly weapons. Good trophies are waiting for you inside!
-------------
Counter-Terrorists: Do not let the terrorists to destroy this important strategic points. Hold down this station at all costs! Mr. Wallace Breen would be very proud of you, when he returns.

Attention, is wanted! - Gordon Freeman, former scientist physicist. Extremely dangerous! He leads several groups of rebels-terrorists. Wanted for the third time! ,)
--------------
Credits:
Source Version by Valve.
Transformed map from "HL2: Deathmatch" in map for "CS: Source" by Dmitry Ghervas.